[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What event is taking place during the opening scene of the 1958 portion of the movie The Godfather Part II?", "correct_answer": "Anthonys First Communion", "incorrect_answers": ["Connies Wedding", "Micheals Birthday", "A Celebration of the Corleones receiving a Gambling license"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the two classes into which ink is divided?", "correct_answer": "Printing and Writing", "incorrect_answers": ["Printing and Office", "Writing and Lining", "Printing and Balling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, who played Juror #4 in the movie 12 Angry Men, also starred as Ev Hillman in the The Tommyknockers.", "correct_answer": "E. G. Marshall", "incorrect_answers": ["Lee J. Cobb", "Karl Malden", "John Fiedler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do scientists calculate the age of a fish?", "correct_answer": "They count the growth rings on the ear bone.", "incorrect_answers": ["They count all the teeth in the fishs mouth.", "They measure the size of the fish and compare that to the average size of that type of  fish.", "They count the teeth in the fishs lower lip."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two countries border the Dead Sea?", "correct_answer": "Jordan and Israel", "incorrect_answers": ["Lebanon and Jordan", "Syria and Jordan", "Lebanon and Israel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Japan suffers from this event very often. It is the sudden, light or violent movement of the earths surface caused by the release of energy in the earths crust.", "correct_answer": "Earthquake", "incorrect_answers": ["Volcano", "Tide", "Tsunami"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2006 movie Superman Returns, opening titles reveal that Superman has been absent from Earth for five years. Where was he during this period?", "correct_answer": "Krypton", "incorrect_answers": ["His hometown", "The Sun", "College"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The acids which the Coca-Cola beverage contains make it harmful to drink.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What island is shared by Indonesia and the nation of East Timor?", "correct_answer": "Timor", "incorrect_answers": ["New Guinea", "Borneo", "Flores"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Disney movie contains the line, A fine conscience I turned out to be!?", "correct_answer": "Pinocchio", "incorrect_answers": ["Lady and the Tramp", "Petes Dragon", "The Little Mermaid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A mermaid is the symbol of this European city; depicted on its coat of arms, it can be seen on statues throughout the city.", "correct_answer": "Warsaw", "incorrect_answers": ["Amsterdam", "Rotterdam", "Copenhagen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a scene from the movie Pretty Woman Julia Roberts character is taking a bath and listening to her walkman. What song is she singing?", "correct_answer": "Kiss by Prince", "incorrect_answers": ["Material Girl by Madonna", "Like a Virgin by Madonna", "Bad Girls by Donna Summer"]}]